<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ALL ABOUT JHARKHAND</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home__page">HOME_PAGE</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="rate_app_title">Rate our App</string>
    <string name="rate_app_message">If you like our app, please take a moment to rate it in play store!</string>
    <string name="dialog_app_rate">Rate App</string>
    <string name="dialog_ask_later">Later</string>
    <string name="dialog_your_feedback">Your Feedback</string>
    <string name="app_message"> you visited %d times</string>

    <string name="text1"> How will I know about my nearby location like hopitals, Schools
        etc?</string>

    <string name="text2">  To know about near by location of hospitals, schools,etc.. you need to
        go to map your location menu. The map will initially show you your current location.Now
        click
        on Hopital button, it will show you your near by hospitals, accordingly click on other
        buttons to get information.
    </string>

    <string name="text3">How to ask query?</string>
    <string name="text4">Go to Query menu from navigation drawer. Now submit few
    details
    about yourself  like
    Name ,
    Email &amp; Phone no. and post your query. Your query will be responded shortly.
</string>
    <string name="text5"> How to give Feedback ?</string>

    <string name="text6">To give feedback.  Write your name,Email &amp;amp; phone no. then submit your
        feedback. The
        person from
        Administration will contact if your
        feedback are appreciating.
    </string>
    <string name="text7"> How do I get the weather information of any other place?</string>
    <string name="text8">Just write your city name, click on ok. It will automatically show you
        temperature in
        celsius along with weather condition.
    </string>
    <string name="text9">How to know about other districts which are not available in app?
    </string>
    <string name="text10"> To know about other district click on button ""Know about other
        districts"" in the respective section, provided at the end.  </string>


    <string name="text50">All About Jharkhand is an informative app to facilitate the people of
        Jharkhand about the various demographic and non-demographic information.\n
        It not only provides information about various sectors of Jharkhand like Population Growth
         Tourist places, Literacy Rate, Gender ratio etc,etc,.. but also give its user the
        details of climate(to plan beforehand the visit to any district), location of nearby places
        like hospitals, schools ..\n
        Users have an option to ask query about
        their district problems  and
        submitting their positive or negative feedback to government,which would help government
        to pay attention to the issues.\n
        At last, we have added quiz to check user knowledge about Jharkhand state.
    </string>

    <string name="text60"> The basic objectives of our App are:-\n
        #  to empower people to add voice regarding development of Jharkhand state\n
        #  allowing them to give feedback to improve their locality.\n
        #  to facilitate people with all demographic and non demographics information\n
        #  providing details of nearby location of essential places like hospitals, schools etc.\n
        # adding a quiz to check user knowledge about Jharkhand State.\n
   </string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">ABOUT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps2">Map</string>
</resources>
